The next one's on its way!
We're playing!
Aaaaaah!
Parry!
The more time I can buy, the
better chance they have to escape!
I'm just going to run around and
parry every single thing I see!
I was finally able to stop!
What?
Who's this old-timer?
I'll be in your eyes.
I'm not to do the world.
That's what I want.
If you don't have to see me?
You can just see me.
You can see me.
I'm not to do the world.
I want to see you.
What are you?
Thank you.
But in the future, in the future,
When a child and a body were burning,
of the power of the
power of
the
power.
Even the horse has a
whole sparkly gold outfit.
Why would he be standing in
a war zone looking all fancy?
Maybe the poor guy is lost or something.
Whatever.
Now's not the time to get distracted, Nor.
I won't stand a chance
if these soldiers gather
up their weapons and
come at me all at once.
I'll have to keep parrying them.
Keep their weapons out of their hands.
Not sure what that is?
But I'm gonna get it too. I
still
can't
help but wonder.
What this old guy's doing out here?
What the devil just happened!
Oh right.
I can't give the soldiers
time to pick up their stuff.
I also got to remember to breathe
every once in a while or I'll pass out.
Wait a second, were you not?
He's going to kill me.
Does the sparkly old man, does he know me?
Nah, we've never met before.
But geez, he's crazy.
He's gonna get hurt out here.
Well, I guess he does have
a sword if he needs it.
Stay focused, Nora.
You've just gotta keep doing your part.
I'm pretty sure that sparkly gold old man
is going to get hurt if he stays out here.
Please, you must tell me who you are.
And why haven't you killed me yet?
Oh, the poor guy thinks I
came here to take him out.
Well, I guess I can't really blame him.
Oh, not that weapon.
Oh, don't be.
I don't want him to be afraid of me.
I need to do something to reassure
him, to let him know I'm not hostile.
Is this working?
Nope, guess not.
Didn't work at all.
I'm getting tired.
I've really been going
nonstop this whole time.
And Low Heel can't do anything
to relieve exhaustion like this.
Lynn.
Inez.
Rolo.
I hope you get out safely.
Shooting Star!
That skill.
Drag race!
It's you.
Oh, good to see you, Grill, Grizzly,
uh, uh, Glibbery? It's Gilbert.
Uh, uh, you did all this?
Nice of you to finally join us, Master.
Sorry.
Wait, you're the...
Hm.
I do not know who you are, but thank you.
We will take care of the rest.
We must at least handle the cleanup,
or it will stain the honor of the
6th Troop of the Royal Capital.
Thousand Blades!
I remember! That's...
that's the power of the swordsman!
The one I've always dreamed of being!
Oh dear.
And after I warned him against
any excessive killing...
Oh ho ho!
That's a tall order, isn't it?
Especially when we're faced
with such a vast army!
Well, corpses will not
provide us any needed intel.
I find the living to be
immensely more cooperative,
especially after bringing back missing
limbs over and over with healing magic.
Hmm.
That's a joke.
Well, it doesn't quite sound
like a joke whenever you say it.
Oaken, they should be
arriving any minute now.
Be ready.
Don't have to tell me.
We have been strung along by the
enemy long enough for my taste.
Now it's my time to shine.
Oh-ho!
Their eyes are as red as fire.
You seem to be enjoying this, Oaken.
But of course.
A good battle is always
riveting no matter what it is.
No matter how long in the tooth I may get.
Now, shall we add the final touches?
Soul Prison!
It's our turn now. Let's go.
Time to save all the survivors and
make them turn over a new leaf.
Oh, wow.
They're the instructors who
taught me at the training schools.
I can't believe I'm
getting to see them again.
Hang on. Is that...?
It is.
That's Noor.
Thanks a lot, Lin.
I'm feeling a lot better now.
All right, but are you sure you're okay?
You should really rest a little longer.
I've gotten enough rest.
I think I can move around again.
I am really hungry, though.
A commanding officer confessed
under Sane's interrogation.
They have no more troops.
They already threw everything
at us, including the dragon,
as well as all the other beasts
that attacked the capital.
But I'm afraid the Emperor
has escaped. The Emperor?
That decrepit old fogey showed up
here on the battlefield? He did.
He must have been very
confident in his chances.
Ho-ho-ho!
Dumb move for a guy who demands
his people call him a wise ruler.
That old geezer must
be losing his marbles.
Old geezer?
That terrified old gray fella?
Hold on.
Do you know who we're
talking about, young man?
I think.
I just met a guy.
He was riding a horse all
decked out in sparkly gold gear.
I mean, he was hard to miss.
Gold on his horse, huh?
He must have been employing
Aurichalcum's saddle ray.
That's very high-grade equipment that
can support an extensive array of skills.
In which case, it makes sense
how he escaped so quickly.
A seriously wearing all gold.
His fashion sense is as
shabby as his attitude.
If he escapes across the
border, we cannot go after him.
There is a fortress and a heavily
guarded bridge that spans the ravine.
There's no hope of catching up
to him by now with normal means.
If only there was a way for us all to
fly together somehow. You know what?
I think that might actually be possible.
What do you mean, son?
Well, I guess.
Assuming that it's still alive.
What an incredible sight to behold.
Being able to see a legendary creature
up close and personal like this.
This makes living to my old age worth it.
Same here.
This must be the first time I've ever
been tasked with healing a dragon.
Well, well, Noor.
You've really grown
quite a lot, haven't you?
I didn't know it was you.
Pardon?
This man?
Is Noor you say? That's right.
It took me a few minutes to recognize him.
Yeah.
Been a while since I've seen you. Ho-ho!
I hadn't the slightest
idea it was you at all.
And you're much larger
than you used to be.
I'm glad to see that you're still alive.
Excuse me?
That is not a very nice
thing to say now, is it?
It is well within my abilities to live
another hundred years or more easily.
And you're still funny too, I see.
I am not telling you a joke.
But listen, Nor, are you sure about this?
Humans riding on the back of a dragon
seems like a terrible idea to me.
Don't worry about that.
We've got Rolo with us. Huh?
Well now, Rolo, my boy, are you
confident in this ability of yours?
No, sir.
I have no confidence at all.
Oh, ho, ho.
You'll be okay.
You can do this, Rolo.
It seems our dragon is coming, too.
Um, yes, okay.
Are you absolutely sure we
should be riding a dragon?
Of course.
Go for it, Rolo.
Um, okay.
Oh, man.
Seems like it's angry.
You can tell?
Only from how it sounds.
I've lived in the mountains for a while.
It wants to get revenge
against those who hurt it.
It would like you to order it to do so.
What now?
You have that much communication
with this large dragon?
Extraordinary!
It's just extraordinary!
Yeah, Rolo is a superstar.
No, I'm really not.
This dragon thinks Norris...
It says it's ready to go now.
All right.
If you're going, get ready. Okay.
You guys are going with them as well?
Yes.
Rolo is the only one who
can speak to the dragon,
so he'll need as much help as he can get.
And S and I will go to guard him.
You'll be joining us too, right?
Wait, what?
Oh, I guess I could.
But, well, I'm really
not good with heights.
I am the one who came up with the idea,
and I dragged Rolo into this, so it
would be awkward now if I didn't.
But still, I mean...
Okay, sure, I'm going to.
Thank you so much!
Having you is like the
strength of a hundred!
I'm coming as well.
I must continue to look after my patient.
Besides, I believe we
have a duty to diplomacy.
Isn't that right?
Don't lump me in with you.
I do not try to intimidate
people with childish mischief.
Wow, you're the...
Thief instructor!
So you're coming too?
I am.
If you're going to fly on this giant beast,
then you'll need the concealment skill.
I can take care of that.
Yes, good point.
All right, I'm coming too.
Oaken, do you not need to
supervise the stone cage?
Okay, fine.
I will go as well.
I believe you will be in need of
a negotiator. Father! Brother!
I'm so glad you're safe!
I guess you've been
pretty worried about us.
I'm glad to see you're safe as well.
You chose to return
instead of going to Mithra.
Yes, I'm willing to accept my
punishment for disobeying your order!
No need, it was my own fault for
giving you such an idiotic command.
I'm relieved you made it back here.
Now Rain, you are in charge of
making any judgment calls out there.
Also, Sir Noor.
Huh, I apologize for always asking,
but please take care of my kids.
Sure, don't even worry about it.
We'll get him back safely.
I'm counting on you
Okay, now fly
Are you sure you're okay with this?
I mean, shouldn't you have
said something to Noor?
We just finally found him after all.
Fact is, he never really needed
us to play a role in his life.
The idea that we would be able
to take him in and raise him?
We were showing our hubris.
Yeah, right, no kidding.
He was like a hero born
straight out of the legends.
I feel pretty silly right now I
I am deeply ashamed of my own laziness.
I should not have been wasting time thinking
I was in any position to teach others!
I am going to retrain myself
from the beginning now
that I've been made aware
of my own shortcomings.
I cannot rest on my laurels
and let my sword rust.
For a guy who's deeply ashamed,
you seem pretty darn happy.
But of course, just think of
the spectacle he showed us.
Yeah, got that right.
After seeing something
like that, who wouldn't be?
Found anything? Nothing.
Any luck there, Lady Lindbergh?
Not a thing.
He's faster than I thought.
Worst case, he may have already
arrived back at the Empire.
beyond that steel bridge the
land turns into empire-controlled
territory we cannot just wildly
rush in there i know we've come
a long way but perhaps we should
consider going back your call
let me think then over there
something is moving extremely fast
that is definitely him
although he's nearing the
imperial capital's defenses
if we cross into their land
we will not make it back
in one piece right now we
are still concealed from
them once they become aware
of our presence the magic
will of course immediately
lose its effectiveness
that's true but letting him
escape is not an option
they have powerful magical
tools and can use them to
reinforce their military power.
We cannot give them any
opportunity to make that happen.
Of course, he's right.
We are already at war.
So, we have no idea what awaits us.
Lord Rain, Lady Lindbergh.
If I may, I would like you to grant
me permission to obliterate this area.
Obliterate?
If this is going to be
our escape route later,
then it would be smart to take out the
defenses while we have the opportunity.
In normal situations, Ines would
never suggest exerting her own power.
But she is just as
angry as the rest of us.
The royal capital she vowed to risk
her life to protect has been flattened.
I agree.
Do as you please, Ines,
and do not hold back.
As you wish.
Divine sword!
Oh, wow.
I believe that will secure our
escape route, Your Majesty.
All right.
Very well done, Ines.
Lin!
Our actions here will determine
the course of the war.
We are going to keep pursuing the Emperor
all the way to the Imperial Capital.
Are you sure you're ready for this? Yes.
Everyone here wields power
far outside the norm.
They are the strongest people imaginable.
There is no need to worry about anything.
Plus above all we have sir nor I
cannot even begin to comprehend
his greatness even now he
Quietly listens to all around him
and he knows the weight of this
moment we shall teach them A hard
lesson about what happens when
you mess with the wrong people?
Thank you so much for watching.
Love you!
What is it worth?
The story is a little more.
The obvious light is perfect.
I have no one else.
No one has to be with you.
Oh